{
    "subject": "Max_Jacoby",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Dust__2009_film_",
    "human_readable": "Max Jacoby directed the film Dust (2009).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7944550514221191,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Max Jacoby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7628563046455383,
            "question": "Who directed the film Dust?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7465267181396484,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Max Jacoby."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6922957301139832,
            "question": "What other films has Max Jacoby directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6905253529548645,
            "question": "Is Max Jacoby a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.549187958240509,
            "question": "What year was the film Dust released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5320990085601807,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of Dust (2009)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3397657871246338,
            "question": "What genre is the film Dust likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.317818820476532,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with the film Dust?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2702752649784088,
            "question": "Where was Dust filmed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Max Jacoby directed the film Dust (2009).",
            "html": "yago_12236_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any awards associated with the film Dust?",
            "html": "yago_12236_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Dust likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_12236_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of Dust (2009)?",
            "html": "yago_12236_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12236_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12236_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12236_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12236_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12236_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12236_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12236_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12236_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12236_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12236_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain multiple references to Max Jacoby directing a film called \"Dust\" in 2009. This can be confirmed through various files (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12236/re-ranker-msmarco/65.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12236/re-ranker-msmarco/92.txt, etc.), where Max Jacoby is mentioned as the director of \"Dust\", along with other details about the film and its production."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports this triple. Specifically, they mention that Max Jacoby directed the feature film \"Dust\" in 2009."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}